所以说 扩散率等于什么鬼
So the rate of diffusion equals something
乘以什么鬼的平方根
times the square root of...something...
我放弃了
I give up.
就快了嘛
Aw, so close.
给姐闭嘴
Shut up.
别着急 你能学会的
Hey, don't worry. You'll get it.
其实很多著名的科学家都是女人
You know, a lot of famous scientists are women.
但都是肥婆 对吧
They're fat, though, right?
走吧 艾丽克斯 要去上大提琴课了
Come on, Alex. It's time for your cello lesson.
辅导得怎么样了
How's the tutoring going?
你听说过这么一句话吗
Are you familiar with the term
"赔了夫人又折兵"
"throwing good money after bad"?
你听说过这么一句话吗
Are you familiar with the term
"邓菲小姐 孤独终老"
"Dunphy, party of one"?
-这就是你的下场 -姑娘们
- Because you will be. - Girls.
海莉其实学得不错 邓菲夫人
Haley's coming along really well, Mrs. Dunphy.
很好 很好
Good. Good.
关键是你要时不时地歇一下
Well, the key is to take a lot of little breaks
这样你就不会郁闷得想要放弃了
so you don't get frustrated and want to quit.
明白
Got it.
我是在和戴维说
I was talking to David.
走吧 宝贝儿
Come on, sweetie.
我只是说 她以后肯定找不到工作
I'm just saying -- she's never gonna get a job,
不过没准她能傍上某个中东富豪
and how do we know the right middle-eastern businessman
对她很好呢
wouldn't treat her great?
我把购物清单落家了
I left my shopping list inside.
告诉你 我们计划让她以后跟你蹭吃蹭喝
For the record, we thought she could live with you.
你们别指望能找得到我
Like I'm gonna tell any of you where I live.
海莉
Haley!
怎么了
What?
我做对题以后才有得亲呢
We only do this when I get one right.
妈咪早该到了
Momma should be here by now.
不会出啥岔子了吧
I wonder what's keeping her.
小卡 这就要看她是开那辆老破车来呢
Well, Cam, that depends. Did she take her jalopy
还是开什么新式小灰机呢
or one of them new fancy flyin' machines?
呸 人家密苏里州
You know, Missouri is more cosmopolitan
比你说的要现代化得多 米奇尔
than you give it credit for, Mitchell.
充满了活灵活现的牛仔田园风情
It's got a very vibrant cowboy-poetry scene.
你上下两句话都不是同一个意思诶
I'm not sure you're making the point that you think --
她来了 过来 热情点 热情点
That's her. Come on. Look alive. Look alive.
妈咪
Momma!
小心肝宝贝儿
Oh, my baby!
亲亲小淘气 过来香一个
Oh, my little bomber. Puppy kiss.
米奇尔 快过来啦
Mitchell, get over here!
巴布 你好吗
Aah, hey, Barb!
我宝贝的宝贝 你好吗
Oh, my baby's baby! How are you?
不是我自吹自擂
Well, I don't want to overstate this,
不过我妈是世界上最棒的女人
but my mom is the greatest woman that ever lived.
小卡爱死他妈了
Cam loves his mom.
她一人养活了四个娃 俩农场
She raised 4 kids, 2 barns,
还有很多其它乱七八糟的
and a whole lot of hell.
听着跟乡村歌曲似的
Well, that sounds like a country song.
没错 歌名就是
And that song would be called
"世界上最棒的女人"
"The Greatest Woman that ever Lived".
小卡爱死他妈了
Cam loves his mom.
从我第一次见到巴布起
From the minute I met Barb,
她就一直开明 热情 并且体贴
she has been open and loving and -- and caring.
我想死你这对小肩膀了
Oh, I have missed these shoulders!
不过要是我有任何意见的话
If I had one complaint --
说起来我还真有个意见
and I do --
那就是 她老对我动手动脚
it's the...inappropriate putting of her hands on my body.
巴布 我买了你做馅要用的小红莓
Hey, Barb. I got you the cranberries you wanted for the stuffing.
你太贴心啦
Oh, bless your heart.
我来帮你吧
Let me get in there and help ya.
捏捏更健康
And a horsey bite.
我好喜欢这样粘在一起哦
This is how I like to cuddle.
这个现象已经 已经有些日子了
It's been -- it's been going on a long time.
杰 陪我去逛商场吧
Jay, you want to go to the mall with me?
不了 我今天胃有点不舒服
No, actually, my stomach's a little funny today.
这可不得了呀 小宝贝
Oh, I am so sorry, papi.
要不咱先买个婴儿床
Maybe we'll stop first at the crib store,
把你放进去 再配条小裙子 好不
and you lay down, and I buy you a little dress, huh?
歌洛莉亚觉得我们美国人都很娇气
Gloria thinks Americans are babies.
在俺们哥伦比亚 像是小感冒
Well, in Colombia, we couldn't go running to the hospital
或者肩膀脱臼什么的 根本用不着去医院
for every little sniffle or dislocated shoulder.
好咧 搞定
Okay. Good.
五比六 我发球 对吧
5-6. I serve. Huh?
杰 你都有什么症状
Jay, what are your symptoms?
恶心 腹胀吗
Nausea, bloating?
曼尼 我不是跟你说
Manny, what did I say about getting off
少上那个医疗网站吗
that crazy doctor website?
我只是担心杰
I'm just worried about Jay.
胃痛可能是多种疾病的征兆
Stomach pains can mean a lot of things --
像是肠梗阻
intestinal blockage...
你发烧吗
Do you have a fever?
够了 曼尼 他好着呢
Stop it! Manny, he's fine.
-跟他说你好着呢 -我好着呢
- Tell him you're fine. - I'm fine.
很好 上车去吧
Okay, good. Get in the car.
在家没事 逛街就得发病
Uh, home fine, not mall fine.
杰 你知道我生着气去逛街的后果
Jay, you know what happens when I shop angry.
我会帮你挪出地儿来的
I'll clear a space.
我看你脸色蜡黄
I'm not loving your color.
一边儿玩去
Go play.
别逞强哦
Don't be a hero.
弱智男配弱智女
So, dumb guys go for dumb girls,
聪明男也要配弱智女吗
and smart guys go for dumb girls?
那聪明女配谁
What do the smart girls get?
配猫吧
Cats mostly.
海莉 我为你们俩的胡搞
So, Haley, how long have I been paying this guy
买单多久了
to make out with you?
大概一个礼拜了吧
Uh, about a week.
我一开始亲他只是想让他闭嘴
First it was just to shut him up,
不过现在我真有点动心了
but now I'm starting to like him.
你要是真喜欢他
If you really like him, though,
就赶紧把迪兰甩了
you have to break up with Dylan.
什么 不要啊
What? No!
相信我
Believe me --
早死早超生
and it's best for everybody if you just do it quickly.
真不敢相信你们居然这样说
I can't believe we're having this conversation.
他就像自家人一样
He's like part of the family.
相信我 这是百利而无一害
Trust me -- it's the right thing to do.
赶紧把他甩了吧
Just end it.
好吧 但是要温柔点
Okay, but be gentle.
青春期的男孩都很敏感的
Boys are surprisingly sensitive at that age.
又来了 水球女的故事
Water-polo-girl story.
没错 我就要讲水球女的故事
Yes, I'm gonna tell the water-polo-girl story,
因为人家真的很伤心
'cause it hurt!
那时候我在校长办公室工作
Okay, so I'm working in the principal's office.
她就那么走进来
She walks in,
头发因刚游完泳而闪闪发亮
hair all silver from the chlorine...
她说她想把棒球外套拿回去
tells me she wants her varsity jacket back.
我一听这个眼睛就湿了
I tear up a little,
接着嚎啕大哭
then I tear up a lot.
我求她 求她不要这样对我
I'm begging, I'm begging --
结果我突然发现
at some point I realize
我屁股底下坐着的是
I'm sitting on the button
全校广播的开关
to the high-school intercom system.
不许笑
Yuk it up, ladies.
从前不好笑 现在更不好笑
Wasn't funny then, is not funny now.
那完全就是杯具啊 海莉
It was traumatic, Haley.
不要像"大炮"琳达对我那样对待迪兰
Don't do Dylan like Linda "the cannon" Concannon did me.
亲爱的
Oh, honey...
都过去那么久了
that was a long time ago.
我真的爱过她
I loved her.
好吧 我知道了
Okay. I know.
你知道吗
You know what?
也许海莉跟迪兰分手以后 我可以打给他聊聊
Maybe I'll call Dylan after he talks to Haley.
他肯定需要找个人来依靠一下
He's gonna need someone to lean on.
但那个人不该是他前女友的老爸
But that someone should not be his ex-girlfriend's father.
亲爱的 迪兰跟海莉分手以后
Honey, when Dylan is out of her life,
就应该跟咱们都分手
he should be out of ours.
你一向讨厌迪兰
You've always hated Dylan.
我没有一向讨厌迪兰
I have not always hated Dylan.
我只是一向认为海莉可以找个更好的
I have always thought that Haley could do better.
再说 这个新男友超聪明呢
Plus, the new boyfriend is so smart.
搞掂了 我们分手了
It's done. We broke up.
什么
What?!
我发了短信给迪兰 分了
I texted Dylan. It's over.
肯定是他
I'll bet that's him.
哭丧着脸的表情
Sad-face emoticon!
透过电话都知道他有多伤心
You can feel the hurt through the phone!
吃晚餐时 小卡的妈妈有一半的时间
Cam's mom's been half of the dinner with her hands
都在对我上下其手
all over me.
就好像她是个瞎子
It was like she was blind
然后想知道我的大腿长什么样
and wanted to know what my thighs looked like.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你对这种事情真的有评论权吗
I mean, are you really the best judge of this kind of a thing?
你从小就对界限模糊
You've had boundary issues since you were a kid.
我才没有
I have not!
好吧 对不起 是我的错
Okay. Sorry. My mistake.
肯定是小卡母亲的错 是她有问题
Must be Cam's mom...her issues.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
-没干吗 拿个勺子而已 -别这样
- Nothing -- just getting a spoon. - Stop it.
-你觉得不舒服吗 -是的
- Is it bothering you? - Yes, it is.
-嘿 米奇尔 -克莱尔 别这样
- Hey, Mitchell - Claire, stop it! Stop it!
-米奇尔 米奇尔 米奇尔 -别逼我
- Mitchell, Mitchell, Mitchell, Mitchell -- - Force field!
还是那么好玩
That never stops being fun.
很好
Good.
听好了 这不是我瞎想的 克莱尔
Listen, this is -- this is not in my head, Claire.
而且她愈演愈烈了
And it's actually getting worse.
小卡怎么说
What does Cam say?
他根本就没注意到
Well, he never seems to notice.
而我肯定不能告诉他
And I certainly can't talk to him about it
因为我绝对不能说他妈坏话
because God forbid I say anything negative about his mom.
有一次我在她的砂锅炖肉里加了盐
One time I added salt to her casserole...
结果他冲进车库砸了我的车
...and he went into the garage and punched the car.
好吧 米奇尔 如果这一切是真的
Okay, Mitchell, if this is happening --
虽然我很确定这是你的幻觉
and I'm pretty sure it isn't --
谢谢 你还真是挺我呀
Thank you. Supportive.
那么你就要让小卡看到他妈妈摸你
then you need Cam to see his mom feeling you up
然后交给他去处理
and then make Cam deal with it.
好好想想吧
Think about it.
迪兰
Hi, Dylan.
邓菲太太
Hey, Mrs. Dunphy.
不过现在我跟海莉分手了
Or, I guess, now that Haley and I broke up,
我想我该叫你"克莱尔"
I should call you "Claire".
还是继续叫我邓菲太太吧
Actually, I think we're gonna stick with "Mrs. Dunphy".
进来吧 你还好吗
Come on in. How are you doing?
不怎么样
Not so good.
我不管去哪 都能见到她的脸
I mean, everywhere I look, I see her face.
那是呀 迪兰 你看的是我们的全家福
To be fair, Dylan, that is a family portrait.
我要上去拿我的东西 可以吗
I got to go get some of my stuff. Is that cool?
当然 去吧
Oh, sure. Yeah.
又是她
There she is again!
别往书架上看
Oh, don't look on the bookshelf!
那会让你
You're just gonna...
小子 有时间吗
Hey, kid, you got a minute?
我要那个医学网站的网址
I need the name of that medical website.
不能等我回家再说吗
Can this wait until I'm home?
我正赢得爽着呢
I'm having the round of my life.
我一直在想 我可能有一点
I've been thinking, I might have a couple of those, uh,
你之前说的那些症状
those symptoms you were talking about.
知道了
I see.
别等我了 你继续打吧
You might as well play through.
我还要耽搁一会呢
It's gonna be a while.
我可能是多想了
I mean, I'm probably wrong,
但是我只是想确认一下
but, you know, I just, uh, want to make sure.
-是曼尼吗 -是工作电话
- Is that Manny? - Work.
那么 告诉他们
So, uh, tell them I'll --
我今天下午就发货 好吗
I'll get that order out this afternoon, huh?
她信了吗
Did she buy that?
因为就连我听起来都觉得有点假
Because it sounded fake on this end.
晚点聊 汤姆
I'll talk to you later, Tom.
是汤姆
Tom.
迪兰
Dylan!
迪兰 迪兰 迪兰 迪兰
Oh, Dylan, Dylan, Dylan, Dylan.
邓菲先生
Hey, Mr. Dunphy.
你们俩现在既然分手了
Hey, now that you guys are broken up,
你随便怎么叫我都行
you can call me whatever you want.
菲尔 维他命菲 菲老爸 都行
Phil, Vitamin P., P. Daddy.
好吧 菲尔
Okay, Phil.
好的
Okay.
我会想念这个臭小子的
I'm gonna miss that bad boy.
有时候我手痒痒了
When I forget my own axe,
就进来拨弄一下它
sometimes I come in here and noodle on it.
实际上 我最近也在写首歌呢
Actually, I've been writing a little song of my own.
也许我可以给你弹
Might be able to pluck out a few...
我一直希望这一切只是个梦
You know, I keep on hoping that this is just a dream,
海莉其实没有跟我分手
that Haley and I didn't really break up.
但这不是梦
But it's not a dream...
除非整件事都是个梦
unless the whole thing was a dream
我们从一开始就没在一起过
and we never even dated in the first place.
真奇怪 这跟我写的歌差不多
Weird -- this is kind of what my song's about.
是啊 真奇怪
Yeah. Weird.
我知道这不好受 但是你会好起来的
I know this is tough, but you're gonna be fine.
我高中的时候跟你很像
You know, I was a lot like you in high school...
除了我的头发短点
except my hair was shorter
我玩的不是吉他而是长笛
and my guitar was a flute.
如果你想要把吉他
Well, if you want your own guitar,
咱俩可以
I mean, we could --
咱俩可以一块去买
We could go out and we'd pick you one.
我不 这样好像不太好
Oh, I don't -- I don't know if that's such a good idea.
没错
Yeah. Totally.
那么
Well
我看我还是走吧
I guess I'll get going.
这样一来
So...
我就能 孤独终老了
I can...well, be alone forever.
管它的呢
Uh, what -- what the hell?
咱俩去买吉他吧
Let's go guitar shopping.
棒极了
Awesome.
答应我件事 别 别告诉邓菲太太好吗
Uh, do me a favor. Don't -- don't tell Mrs. Dunphy?
那是一定的 没问题
Yeah. Definitely. You got it.
好的 很好
Okay. All right.
那回头见
Well, I guess I'll see ya.
好的 你
Okay. You --
你可以直接
you, uh, you can go ahead and exit
从 正门出去的
through the...front door.
对哦 我都习惯了
Oh, right. Habit.
我的旧年鉴
My old yearbook!
你知道我把它们都存下来了
You know I saved them all.
-看呀 -是什么
- Oh, look. - What?
你是全校最可爱的男生
"You're the cutest boy in school.
你将拥有一个美妙绝伦的夏天
You're gonna have an awesome summer.
亲亲 布兰达
Smooches -- Brenda."
可怜的布兰达 你将拥有一个
Oh, Brenda, you are about to have
史上最郁闷的夏天
the most confusing summer of your life.
大家好
Hey, guys!
米奇尔回来了
Oh, there's Mitchell!
我的小亲亲
My little corn silk!
巴布 你的拥抱真带劲
Oh, Barb, oh, you are such a good hugger.
她的拥抱是最带劲的不是吗
Isn't she the best hugger?
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
看看我给你带了什么 巴布
Oh, and look what I -- I got you, Barb.
是什么
What's that?
是刮奖彩票
Scratchers!
-亲亲 -谢啦
- Mmm... - Thank you.
真不错
Nice.
你的茶好了 我去给你沏
Oh, that's your tea. I'm gonna get your tea.
谢谢亲爱的
Thanks, honey.
我需要个硬币
Well, I need a quarter.
我来找找看
Oh. Let me have that.
好吧 请随便摸
Oh, wow, yeah, feel free to fish around in there.
小卡 小卡
Cam? Cam.
也给我来一杯 谢谢
I'd like a cup, too, please.
马上就好
Just a second.
巴布 我跟你讲
Ohh, Barb, ohh. You know what?
我 我今天扭伤了
I-I-I strained myself so bad today.
哪里疼
Well, what's hurtin' on ya?
就在 后背下面
It's this area between my, uh, lower back
大腿上面这块
and upper thigh.
听起来像是屁股
Sounds like your fanny.
对 就是屁股
It's my fanny.
疼得不得了
It's really knotted up.
你得找个医生看看
Well, you need someone to work on that.
我倒是想 只是我疼得走不动了
Ohh, I would love that. Just -- it's really seized up.
我只要你来捏捏
Just put your fingers all over my...
我的屁股就好了
my fanny.
用你的回春之手 巴布
Your magic fingers...Barb.
老妈 你的茶好了
Momma? Your tea.
-米奇尔 -谢谢 宝贝
- Mitchell? - Thanks, sweetie.
能否借一步说话
See you in the room for a minute?
谢谢 茶还很烫
Thank you. It's very hot.
-别烫着舌头 -好的 亲爱的
- Don't burn your tongue. - All right, honey.
好吧 我不会哭
Okay, I am not gonna cry,
但是我想知道为什么 米奇尔
but I want to know why, Mitchell,
你为什么在我妈面前表现得跟只狒狒一样
Why you are presenting to my mother like a baboon.
我想让你看看她是怎么摸我的
I wanted you to see her fondling me.
看来你就是承心要弄哭我
So, you do want me to cry.
不 不 小卡 只是
No, no, Cam, it's just that...
她总是对我动手动脚
she's always touching me inappropriately,
而你似乎从来没有注意到
and you never seem to notice.
做给我看 米奇尔
Show me, Mitchell.
用莉莉的娃娃做给我看 我妈摸你哪了
Show me on Lily's doll where my mother is touching you.
我知道你不爱听 但是她确实动手动脚
I know that you don't want to hear this, but she's handsy,
让我觉得很不自在
and it makes me uncomfortable.
天啊 我知道这是怎么回事了
Oh, my god. I know what this is.
我妈太关心你了 你一时适应不了
You're just not used to having a mother that shows affection.
别又把我妈扯进来
Oh, do not make this about my mother.
我没有
I didn't.
但是跟母亲的肢体接触是难免的
But it is normal for a mother to be physical.
偶尔的拥抱或者
And it is not strange
拍拍屁股是很正常的
for an occasional hug or a little pat on tanny.
她不只是拍 小卡 根本不是
Okay, these aren't pats, Cam -- no.
她一直揪来揪去不放手
She squeezes and lingers!
跟我示范下她怎么揪来揪去不放手了
Show me where she squeezes and lingers.
小卡 把娃娃放下
Cam, put the doll down.
我不知道她是开放还是疯掉了
I don't know if this is just sexual or -- or crazy town,
但是她老是对我下咸猪手
but your mother cannot keep her hands off of me,
我已经受不了了
and it's creeping me out
不
No.
巴布
Barb...
我给你示范
Let me show you
你在哪捅了我妈一刀
where you stabbed my momma.
谢谢你帮我挑吉他
Thanks for helping me pick out my axe.
还有你说得对
You were so right, by the way.
双颈吉他的确是太过了
The one with two necks would have been overkill.
你想吃就吃吧
If you want, you can have some of that.
明天开始节食
Diet starts tomorrow!
这也不能告诉邓菲太太哦
Don't tell Mrs. Dunphy about this, either.
我 一直想跟海莉来这里
I, uh, I always wanted to go to this place with Haley,
但是她觉得很傻
but she said it looked stupid.
她为人太主观了
She's a girl with strong opinions --
跟她妈妈一样
like her mother.
克莱尔总是对我买的这件运动衫指指点点
Claire hates this new sweatshirt I bought.
她说这看上去像是
She says it looks like something
女生去沙滩时穿的衣服
a girl would wear to the beach.
确实很像
Yeah, it does.
但我还是穿了
But I wear it anyway.
明白我的意思吗
See?
我觉得吧 一个人要是不能做喜欢的事
I figure, why be alive if you can't do the things
活着还有啥意思
you're passionate about?
那么你热衷于什么呢 迪兰
What are you passionate about, Dylan?
额 我一直想开车去格雷斯兰
Uh, I always wanted to drive to Graceland.
不错 还有呢
Fun! What else?
我认识一个人能给我搞到一只美洲山猫
I know a guy who can get me a pet bobcat.
不行 你根本不知道它们多厉害
Yeah! No, you don't really know what they're gonna do.
重点是 你人生道路还长着呢
The point is, you got your whole life ahead of you.
享受单身吧
Enjoy being single.
我觉得我应该给你弹一下这首歌
I really got to play that song for you.
我突然来感觉了
This is all in there.
好啊
Yeah.
酷毙了 我马上回来
Awesome. Be right back.
嘿 你 过来
Hey, hey, come here.
那边那家伙是跟别人一起来的吗
Is that guy over there with someone?
你知道他们在搞什么吗
Could you tell if there was anything going on between them?
不知道
I don'know.
好像在说一起去格雷斯兰什么的
They were talking about taking a trip to Graceland together.
他想去是因为
He just wants to go
他觉得那是一个游乐园
'cause he thinks it's an amusement park!
我得跟你说
I got to tell you,
你这症状越来越像憩室炎了
this is looking more and more like diverticulitis.
有没有说如何治疗
Do they say how to treat it?
像是用电热毯或者 又疼了
Like a heating pad or -- ohh -- there it is again.
说说你是怎么个疼法
Well, describe the pain.
就像被捅了一刀
It's like I'm being stabbed,
但又像是被我吃掉的扇贝
but also like I ate a bad scallop
从里面捅了我一刀一样
that's stabbing me from the inside.
很形象 但网站上没这些选项
That's colorful, but there's no box for that.
你们爷俩干啥捏
What are you guys looking at?
-看美女 -赫芬顿邮报 美女
- Girls! - Huffington post...girls.
曼尼 让老娘看看
Manny, let me see that screen.
我不是叫你不要上这个网站的吗
What did I tell you?
不是他的错 是我让他看的
It's not his fault. I asked him to look.
我开始觉得我的病严重起来了
I'm starting to think I have a serious problem here.
没错 就是这破电脑惹的祸
Yes, you do! That computer!
你看了网页 就开始想入非非
You read it there, you think it here,
然后就无病呻吟
you feel it here.
你想好受点吗
You want to feel better?
好了 你痊愈了
There -- you're cured.
帮我争取15分钟时间
Give me 15 minutes,
弗罗伦斯·南丁格尔女士要是问起来就说我去医院了
then tell Florence Nightingale I went to the hospital.
我要杀了她 我还要杀了他
I'm gonna kill her! I'm gonna kill him!
我要杀了这对狗男女
I'm gonna kill both of them!
怎么了
What happened?
迪兰找了个新女友
Dylan has a new girlfriend!
什么时候
When did that happen?
管他呢
Who cares?
他什么都没跟你说么
I'm just surprised he didn't say anything...
奇怪了
to you.
他也不回我短信
He's not answering my texts.
他怎么能这么对我
How could he do this to me?!
亲爱的 是你把他甩了的
Oh, honey, you were the one who broke up with him.
我没想到他那么快又找了一个
I didn't think he was gonna find someone so fast!
可能他比我想的要好
Maybe he's better than I thought.
不 不会 绝对不会
No, he's not. What? No, he's not better!
知道谁更好么
No, you know who's better?
戴维 家教哥戴维
David -- David the tutor.
聪明的戴维
Smart, smart David?
可能是他来了
Maybe that's him right now!
想跟他单独相处吗
Do you want the house to yourself?
就一会儿
For just a little while.
我收到你的短信了
I got your texts.
你骂得还真狠
You swore a lot.
她是谁
Who is she?
谁是谁
Who is who?
你的新女友
Your new girlfriend.
我要她的名字和地址 好去找她算账
I need her name and address, so I can mess her up.
我哪有新女友了
I don't have a new girlfriend.
别装傻了 迪兰
Don't play dumb, Dylan.
我没有 我从来不装傻
I'm not. I'm never playing dumb!
我在那个傻逼餐厅看到你了
I saw you at that stupid restaurant,
你跟她椅子上的恶心运动衫同吃一个圣代
sharing a sundae with her ugly sweatshirt on the chair.
是那个贱人吗
Oh, is that the skank?
不不 没有 没有什么荡妇
No...no, there's -- there's no skank.
那你为什么不接电话
Well, then why aren't yo answering it?
因为我想跟你谈谈
'Cause I want to talk to you.
我倒是想跟她谈谈
Well, I want to talk to her.
我要给她打回去
I'm gonna call her back
让她把她的爪子从属于
and tell her to keep her hands off
我的东西上拿开
of what belongs to me.
-海莉 -喂
- Haley... - Hello.
-爸 -海莉
- Dad? - Haley?
我的天 那件运动衫
Oh...my...god -- the sweatshirt?
跟迪兰在一起的人是你吗
That was you with Dylan?!
等一下 你就是那个新女友吗
Wait, you're the other girl?
不 我们只是朋友
No, we're just friends!
菲尔 你搞什么
Phil, what are you --
好了 把电话挂了
Okay, put the phone down.
到底是怎么回事
what is going on?
他需要一个可以倾诉的人
He needed someone to talk to.
他的心都快碎了
He took the break-up pretty hard.
-但是 -真的吗
- But -- - You did?
我一直希望我们能重归于好
I mean, I kept on hoping that we'd get back together.
一想到你跟别人在一起我都快疯了
Thinking of you with someone else just drove me crazy.
我也是 宝贝
Me too, baby.
但是你爸帮我认识到
But then your da helped me figure out
也许分开才是最好的选择
maybe it's best if we're apart.
好样的
Nice.
我只是觉得
I mean, I think I just need
我需要一点时间去跟迪兰约会
a little time to date...Dylan.
是说我自己啦 不是另一个叫迪兰的人
And I mean me, not another guy named Dylan.
所以 我们还是要分手吗
So, we're still broken up?
是的 我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
好吧 那就 再见吧
Wow. Okay...um...I don't know -- I'll see you.
再见
Bye.
你没事吧 宝贝
Are you okay, baby?
还要垫多个枕头吗
Do you need another pillow?
我知道你觉得我没事
I know you think this is nothing,
但医生的确说有可能是溃疡
but he did say it could be an ulcer.
他还说有可能是胀气
He also said it could be gas.
你想让我帮你拍拍背吗 过来 过来
Do you want me to burp you? Come here. Come here.
十有八九是憩室炎
Dollars to doughnuts, it's diverticulitis.
不是憩室炎
Actually, it's not.
你得了急性阑尾炎
You have acute pendicitis.
我们要马上给你动手术
We need to get you into surgery right away.
紧急手术 我跟你说了不是小毛病
Emergency surgery. I told you it was something.
不可能 你得再复查一下
That can't be right. You have to check again!
已经确诊了
The tests are conclusive.
一切都会没事的 普里契特先生
Everything will be all right, Mr. Pritchett.
咱们走吧
Let's go.
不 杰 如果是真的话
No, jay, if that's true,
那我就是全世界最恶毒的老婆了
yhen I'm the worst wife in the whole wide world!
我让你忍了整整两天
I made you suffer for two whole days!
亲爱的 没事的
Honey, it's okay.
不 怎么会没事
No, it's not okay!
为什么 为什么我总是差点害死我老公
Why?! Why do I always almost kill my husbands?!
我找时间再听这个故事吧
And I want to hear this story sometime,
但我现在要准备割阑尾了
but I'm sort of counting down to a rupture here!
不 你不能带着对我的怨恨离开
No!! You can't go without forgiving me!
你要是死在手术室里了怎么办
What if you die in there?
没有你我该怎么办
What do I do without you?!
我原谅你了
I forgive you,
但是没人会死于阑尾炎手术
but nobody dies of an appendectomy!
没错 通常都是麻醉出问题
True, it's usually the anesthesia that gets you.
你六十多岁了 对吧
You're over 60, right?
我永远不会忘了你的 杰
I will never forget you, Jay!!
你还是保持铁石心肠吧 拜托
Could you go back to not caring, please?!
米奇尔 我是巴布
Mitchell, it's Barb.
巴布 我很抱歉
Ohh, Barb. I'm so sorry.
不不 亲爱的 听我说
Well, no, no, honey, you hush.
听着 我
Look, I...
我一直在想关于我听到的
I've been thinking about what I heard, and...
也许我是摸你摸得的有点过分了
maybe I do touch you too much.
我想说我这么做是因为咱们是一家人
And I could say it's 'cause we're a family,
但是 事实上 我不确定
but, you know, I don't know.
我猜我跟你在一起很开心
I guess I have been having some fun with you,
我 我以为摸两把没事的
and I...I thought that it was harmless,
但是我从来没想让你觉得不舒服
but I would never want to make you uncomfortable.
巴布 这也是我的错
Barb, it's my fault, too.
那我们和好了吗
So we're okay?
是的 是的 当然了
Yes, yes, of course.
谢天谢地
Thank god.
因为如果咱俩之间有芥蒂的话
'Cause I couldn't live with myself
我会难受死的
if things stayed weird between us.
-小卡 小卡 -怎么了
- Uh, Cam? Cam? - What is it?
我们已经和好了 宝贝
Well, we got it all worked out, sweetie!
太好了 我去拿相机
Oh, great. Let me get my camera!
没必要吧 不要
Okay, that's not necessary -- no!
从现在开始 如果我做得过分了
From now on, if I go too far,
-拜托你直接告诉我 -好的
- please, you just tell me about it. - Okay.
那是什么
What is that? Oh -- ohh!
差点把手镯丢了
Almost lost my bracelet.
-掉在那还好 -不
- That would be an area that's okay. - No!
-要命 -我来捡 我来捡
- Oh, dang it! - I'll get it. I'll get it.
没事 我看见它掉在哪儿了
Oh, no, I saw where it fell.
别逼我 别逼我
Force field! Force field!
怎么回事
What's going on?
-我把手镯掉进去了 -妈咪
- I lost my bracelet in here. - Momma!
听着 我想这种就是米奇尔
Listen, I think this might be one of those situations
觉得你做的过分的情形之一
where Mitchell feels like you're crossing a boundary.
是吗
Really?
就像 这样也算吗
Like, this too?
那么 我要好好想一想
Well...I...I got to have a good long think
我的行为举止问题了
about how I conduct myself.
我真的很抱歉 米奇尔
I'm truly sorry, Mitchell.
没事 没事
It's okay! It's okay.
那咱们赶紧照张相
Well, let's take one quick picture,
-然后我们就出去 -好的
- and we'll get out of his way. - Yeah. Absolutely.
-靠近一点 -这样行吗
- Scooch together there. - This all right?
好啦
Okay.
我想他
I miss him.
他是你第一个真正意义上的男朋友
He was your first real boyfriend.
我一直希望他能出现
I keep expecting him to show up.
他以前都是晚上过来
He used to come by at night,
然后我偷偷溜去跟他见面
and I'd sneak out to see him.
-是 我知道 -你知道吗
- Yeah, I know. - You knew?
他开一辆没有消音器的三十年前的旧车
His car is 30 years old and doesn't have a muffler.
他居然还按喇叭
And he honked.
我超爱那台车
I loved that car.
我坐着它去吉他店
I rode in it to the guitar store.
感觉自己快飞起来了
I felt like I was flying.
我知道你现在很难过 宝贝 但是
I know it hurts now, sweetheart, but...
这样你才明白这段感情是值得拥有的
that's how you know it was a relationship worth having.
谢谢 爸
Thanks, dad.
迪兰 猫王家好玩吗
So Dylan, you love the Graceland?
是的 没错
Yeah, that's true.
如果他们有过山车就更酷了
Probably would be cooler if they had roller coasters.
不过 能看到国王住的地方还是很有趣对吧
Still, it's fun to see where the king lived, huh?
不 不 不 不
No. No, no, no.
那只是一个比喻 美国没有国王
That's just an expression. America doesn't have a king.
是啊 好呀 什么时候
Yeah. Oh, sure. Uh-huh. When?
并不总是那样的
Well, that's not always the case.
迪兰 你有机会
So, Dylan, did you get a chance
听我发给你的歌吗
to listen to that song I sent you?
没有吗 你有七分钟时间吗
No? You got seven minutes?